[{"answer": "You know, that's a great question because I don't know if I'm wired that way.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "How do they keep it?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "You know, I think it's effort.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Like a madman.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Did you just go party?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "We were doing -- well, we were doing about 20 -- well, the last public quarter, I think, was $13 million, then $18 million, then I think our -- last one after we sold was $25 million for the quarter.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "What was -- what were the revenues in your company when you sold it for $5.9 billion?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Have you done that throughout your life?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "You seem to always say, where's the next edge?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "That part is not hard because once you taste it, I mean, you just got to go back for more.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Because those guys get it?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Are we better off?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Individually, it just depends on your own personal circumstances that you may or may not be better off.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Where are we?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Well, my ring, I can't have it out where I can see it because I just get so fired up and like, so crazy, like let's go.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "You were telling me during the break, what did you say about the ring?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "You know, it's hard to describe.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "What did it mean to you to create that victory with a team after a little less than 10 years, a little more than 10 years, I guess?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "And it's always more of a relief than anything else, you know?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I'm not a big supporter of anybody.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "And what would your report card be for what you think Mitt Romney can do?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "If the Internet hadn't happened for President Clinton, he doesn't have a surplus, right?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "They both scare the hell out of me.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "So how would you rate the parties?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "And we say, OK, what are you going to do to increase profits for this company?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Oh, I always do.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "And you're willing to do that?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "What's a kid supposed to do in a spot like this?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "The notion that a single person, acting alone without anybody watching, can change the course of an enterprise is probably true as much for a company as it is for a country.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Would you share an example of that?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "I -- I don't think, I think the answer to that is now.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Is there a conflict between spirituality and economic success?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Well, it was fun to meet Mark Cuban and to be here with him.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "And if you obviously feel differently, why and what do we need to do to move America forward to start growing again?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "What President Romney can do, we've got -- what we've got in the White House today is a first-rate campaigner and a great speechmaker.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "What's going to get them back in the game?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "Any bill that's 2700 pages, when you -- if you're a citizen and you're looking at this television program, I'm going to make an intemperate statement.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "What would you change?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "YNN: If we take a break --", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Is that your concern?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Tony, Tony, when they take a break at CNN, most likely, you're going to see an argument between Progressive, All State and Geico on how -- on how to get cheaper auto insurance.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "Right now under the Obama the prices are increasing for your employees, is that right?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "You did this with your own company, did you not?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "I got -- I got with my union, the Culinary Union.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "You cut, what, a $1,000 fee from an MRI down to what?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "You're 84 now, right?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "ICKENS: I still have a lot of things to do.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "You're the greatest person I could put out there to dispel it, but how can you help people?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "And I'm running out of time.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "That helps, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "Putting in a fitness center in 1969.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "How did you do that and why are you so focused on health care?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "The -- I started this four years ago.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "What's the plan?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 727, "question": "OBBINS: You've got 51 votes, didn't you?", "qSentId": 726}, {"answer": "Well, this was an amendment to the Transportation Bill.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 729, "question": "So why didn't it get passed?", "qSentId": 728}, {"answer": "No, I'm not, but I get the idea.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "You're following this?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "Well, they voted it non-germane, and I got 51.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "They played with the rules, so you had to get 60 votes instead?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "We have -- you think --", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "So, really, we have more natural gas now than Saudi Arabia?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "We have more natural gas than any country in the world.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "Has oil?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "That's just 200,000, is what it is.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 779, "question": "Why doesn't President Obama step in and say, we're going to take all of the vehicles the US government has and put them on natural gas?", "qSentId": 778}, {"answer": "No, but it - exactly.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "Won't it lead by example?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "Most people are not good at -- most people are not good at changing their styles, how are they going to change their entire culture?", "qSentId": 797}, {"answer": "Well, just because we have the most brains of any country in the world and that we're innovating more rapidly --", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 822, "question": "Scalability?", "qSentId": 821}, {"answer": "Just listen to these two guys is how.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "Steve?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "He has an energy policy that would be successful.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 844, "question": "As opposed to private enterprise?", "qSentId": 843}, {"answer": "Our people.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 852, "question": "What is America's greatest strength going forward?", "qSentId": 851}, {"answer": "Individual initiative, greed, the sense to do better in life, to have a better life.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "What do we have to look forward to?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "This conversation is going to continue after we continue to roll, I have a feeling here.", "docId": "120916pmt", "aSentId": 866, "question": "Mark, is government going to do it?", "qSentId": 865}]